//data/questions.js
const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "In what year was the first official Womens's Rugby World Cup held?",
        options: [1987, 1991, 1995, 1999],
        correctAnswer: 1991,
        type: "multiple-choice",

    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which country hostes the first Womens's Rugby World Cup?",
        options: ["England", "France", "Wales", "New Zealand"],
        correctAnswer: "Wales",
        type: "multiple-choice",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which team has won the most Womens's Rugby World Cup titles?",
        options: ["New Zealand", "England", "Australia", "France"],
        correctAnswer: "New Zealand",
        type: "multiple-choice",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "How many teams participated in the first Womens's Rugby World Cup?",
        options: [12, 16, 20, 24],
        correctAnswer: 12,
        type: "multiple-choice",           
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which player is the all-time leading try scorer in Womens's Rugby World Cup history?",
        options: ["Portia Woodman", "Magali Harvey", "Emily Scarratt", "Kendra Cocksedge"],
        correctAnswer: "Portia Woodman",
        type: "multiple-choice",
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question: "How many players are on the field for each team during a standard game of rugby union?",
        options: [13, 15, 11, 9],
        correctAnswer: 15,
        type: "multiple-choice",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Who won the world cup in 2014?",
        options: ["New Zealand", "England", "Australia", "France"],
        correctAnswer: "England",
        type: "multiple-choice",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "In rugby sevens, how many minutes does each half last?",
        options: [5, 7, 10, 15],
        correctAnswer: 7,
        type: "multiple-choice",
    }, 
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "which Women's rugby tournament is contested annually between England, France, Ireland, Italy, Scotland, and Wales?",
        options: ["Six Nations Championship", "The Rugby Championship", "Pacific Four Series", "Super W"],
        correctAnswer: "Six Nations Championship",
        type: "multiple-choice",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "In Women's rugby sevens at the Olympics, which country won the first gold medal in 2016?",
        options: ["New Zealand", "Australia", "Canada", "United States"],
        correctAnswer: "Australia",
        type: "multiple-choice",
    },
];
export default questions;